Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is oat of this world. Let me show
you how to make it. Today, we're making
this with a vanilla protein shake. You
can also make this with fat-free milk.
I'll have the substitution down in the
caption. And then another key to this
recipe is using a brown sugar substitute
rather than a white sugar substitute.
And also using a little bit of butter
extract. Once you combine everything,
you can throw that in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Take it out, run it
under hot water for about a minute. Then
you can go ahead and throw it in your
creamy. Just run it on the light ice
cream setting. Take it out, see how it's
looking. If it's still super powdery,
run it on the respin setting. If it's
not and looks all right, scrape down the
sides and then hollow out a hole in the
center like this. Then we can grab our
melted chocolate. The ingredients for
this and the process will be down below
in the description as well. And just
pour that down the middle of the pint.
Now, while that is mixing, we can grab
our topping. I use one of these made
good cinnamon bun flavored bars. They're
honestly pretty good, but you can
totally use any kind of brown sugar
cinnamon flavored cookie or bar.
Basically, anything similar to this.